A Guide to the Records of Eastern State Hospital, 1770-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. News Clippings and Summaries, 1964-2008., Extent: 4.275 cu. ft. (Box 38-47.)
  - News Clippings
    - 1987. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 1987. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 1988. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 1988. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - 1989. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 1989. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 1989. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 1989. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 1990. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1990. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1990. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - 1991. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - 1992. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - 1992. (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - 1993. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - 1993. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 1993. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - 1994. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 1994. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 1994. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1995. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 1995. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - 1995. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - 1996. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - 1997. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - 1997. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - 1998. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1998. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 1998. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - 1998. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - 1999. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - 1999. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - 2000. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 2001. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 2002. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 2003. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 2004. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - 2005. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 2006. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - 2007. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - 2008. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Children at Eastern State, 1964. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - "Eastern State Bicentennial," supplement to The Virginia Gazette, 1973. (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Eastern State Hospital investigation, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - "Society's Untouchables," article in The Daily Press/Times Herald, 1985. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - "The Last Word," column in The Virginia Gazette, 1987-1995. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - "The Last Word," column in The Virginia Gazette, 1996-2007. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Western State Hospital investigation, 1981-1983. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries
    - 1989 March. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1989 May. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1989 August. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - 1989 October. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - 1990 January. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - 1990 February. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - 1990 February. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - 1990 March. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - 1990 March. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1990 April. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1990 April. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1990 May. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1990 May. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1990 June. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1990 June. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 1990 July. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - 1990 July. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - 1990 August. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - 1990 August. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 1990 September. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1990 September. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1990 October. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 1990 November. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1991 January. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 1991 February-March. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - 1991 April. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - 1991 May-July. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - 1991 August. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - 1991 September. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 1991 October-December. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - 1992 February. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - 1992 April. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1992 July-August. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 1992 November. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - 1993 September. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - 1994 January. (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Series X. Newsletters, 1948-2008., Extent: 1.125 c.u. ft. (Box 48-50.)
  Contains the newsletter The Eastern Statesman, which was produced by and largely for Eastern State Hospital employees, and to a lesser extent, patients and interested family and community members. The newsletters contain information about hospital policies, activities, and governmental legislation. They also contain photographs of employee activities and events, notations about births, weddings, illnesses, new-hires, retirements, employee service recognitions and other pertinent information. Also included for the years 1956-1957 are copies of the The Literary Statesman which feature stories and poetry, some written by patients. Both The Eastern Statesman and The Literary Statesman were widely distributed outside of the hospital.
  Arranged chronologically by date of publication.
  - 1948. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 1956. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - 1957. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 1958. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 1959. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 1960. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - 1961. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - 1962. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - 1963. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - 1964. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - 1965. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - 1966. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - 1967. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - 1968. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - 1969. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 1970. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - 1971. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - 1972. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - 1973. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - 1974. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - 1975. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - 1976. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 1977. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 1978. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 1979. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 1980. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - 1981. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - 1982. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - 1983. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - 1985. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - 1986. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - 1988. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - 1989. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - 1990. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - 1991. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - 1992. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - 1993. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - 1994. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 1995. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 1996. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 1997. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - 1998. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 1999. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - 2000. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - 2001. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - 2002. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - 2003. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - 2004. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - 2005. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - 2006. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - 2007. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - 2008. (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Series XI. Papers, Speeches and Lectures, 1949-1985., Extent: .225 cu. ft. (Box 51.)
  Contains papers, transcribed speeches and lectures on a variety of topics such as drug addiction, medical conditions, types of therapy employed at Eastern State Hospital, and the use of certain medications. Many of the papers, speeches and lectures were written and/or given by Eastern State Hospital leaders and employees. Material not attributed to a specific author can be found at the end of the list arranged according to the type of document. These items were not included in Series XV. Publications because they are more informal in nature. Early essays and papers written by Dr. John M. Galt can be found in Series IV., Subseries D. Correspondence, Subject Files and Ledgers (Superintendent).
  Arranged alphabetically by the author or speaker's last name.
  - Abbitt, A.W., speech, to Virginia Society of Hospital Pharmacists, 1956. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Alice, paper, "Our 'School' at Eastern State Hospital," 1955. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Campden-Main, B., Dr., lecture, "The Problem of Drug Addiction," undated. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Dowell, R.O., D.D.S., speech, "Medical-Dental Relations," given at a meeting of the Williamsburg-James City County Medical Society, 1949. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Earman, Stella M., suggestions, 1954. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Fisscher, Rolf, paper, "Industrial Therapy," undated. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Frazier, Shervert H., M.D., speech, "Mental Health Services in America: The Unfinished Journey," given at the dedication of the Public Hospital of 1773 at Colonial Williamsburg, 1985. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Granville L., M.D., paper, "Historical Notes on Occupational Therapy at the Eastern State Hospital 100 Years Ago," 1950. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Granville L., M.D., speech, Fourth of July, 1956. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Jones, Granville L., M.D., speech, "The Key to Success with Activity Therapy," at the dedication of the Henry E. Davis building, 1964. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Kirven, Leo E., Jr., M.D., paper, "Community Responsibility in Rehabilitation of the Mentally Ill," 1963. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Lassen, T.J., M.D., speech, "The Effect of Orally Administered Reserpine on Chronic, Disturbed Patients in Mental Hospital," 1955. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Malcom, Ruth, lecture, "Some Aspects of Psychiatric Care at the Children's Unit, Eastern State Hospital," given at the Virginia Conference on Social Work, 1959. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Massie, George B., M.D., paper, "The Early Management of Severely Burned Patients," 1961. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - McIlwain, Jean S., paper, "A Blue Ribbon Home," undated. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Peet, Doris, speech, "The Nurse's Obligation in the Care of the Emotionally Disturbed Child," 1964. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Pile, Wendell J., M.D., et. al., paper, "Multiple Charcot's Joints: A Case History," 1951. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Walls, Dr. Francis G., paper, "Geriatric Problems," 1963. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Lecture, "Orientation for American Legion Auxillary-Hospital Corps," undated. (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Paper, "Admission to Mental Hospitals," undated. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Paper, "Comparative Study of the Use of Diomax and Ammonium Chloride in Senile Patients," 1955. (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Paper, "Development of an Institution for the Treatment of Colored Epileptic and Feeble-Minded in Virginia," 1954. (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Paper, "History and Description of Eastern State Hospital, Williamsburg, Virginia," (Chapter III.), undated. (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Paper, "Patient-Doctor Relationships in the Treatment of Alcoholism," 1961. (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Paper, "The Beginning of Music Therapy in E.S.H.," 1950. (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Series XII. Patient and Medical Treatment Records, 1841-2009., Extent: 1.35 cu. ft., 5 volumes. (Box 52-54;, Volume 148-152.)
  Restricted: patient records containing patient names or information that are less than 125 years old. Some records may require review by an archivist and/or redaction (if it is possible) before they are served. Transorbital lobotomy case book records (A-Z) are closed in their entirety for 125 years from the date of creation.
  This series contains a variety of registers related to patients and medical treatment at the hospital. Included are record books kept by the night watchman and night watch nurse. These volumes document the activities of the nighttime staff and describe the number of visits to each ward, the time and temperature of the ward at the time of the visit, as well as the names of patients and their level of "excitement." Also included are case books that provide medical treatment information, a record of surgical cultures, transorbital lobotomy records and a register of articles belonging to patients which includes a listing of clothing, money, jewelry and other personal effects. This series also contains the art therapy drawings of a patient named Michael Condrey. Researchers interested in admission, statistical and/or patient census information should see Series I. Admission and Statistical Registers.
  Arranged alphabetically by the title of the volume or record.
  - Articles belonging to patients, Record of, 1903-1967. (Volume 148)
  - Case book, 1842-1843. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Case book, Males (with index), 1841-1843. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Drawings by Michael Condrey, 2009. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Drawings by Michael Condrey, 2009. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Drawings by Michael Condrey, 2009. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Drawings by Michael Condrey, 2009. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Drawings by Michael Condrey, 2009. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Female watch (night), Record of, 1861-1862. (Volume 149)
  - Male watch (night), Record of, 1924-1927. (Volume 150)
  - Male watch (night), Record of, 1933-1935. (Volume 151)
  - Surgical cultures, Record of, 1961-1972. (Volume 152)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, A, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ba 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Be-Bo, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Br, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Bu, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ca, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ch-Cl, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Co-Cz, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Da, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, De-Du, 1951-1956. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, E, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, F, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ga-Go, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Gr-Gu, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ha-He, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ho-Hu, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, J, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, K, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, La, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Le-Li, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ma-Mc, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Me-Mo, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, N-O, 1951-1956. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, P, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ra-Ri, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Ro-Ry, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Sa-Se, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Sh-Sn, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Sp-St, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, T, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, U-V, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Wa-We, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Wh-Wy, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book, Z, 1951-1956. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book: Statistical information and reports, 1951-1960. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Transorbital lobotomy case book: "Transorbital Lobotomy at Eastern State Hospital," by Janet Colaizzi, in Journal of Psychosocial Nursing, 1996. (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Series XIII. Personnel Records, 1907-1988., Extent: .225 cu. ft., 1 volume. (Box 55;, Volume 154.)
  This series is composed of two ledgers of employee records. The earliest ledger includes names, beginning date of employment, rate of wages or salary, and occasionally notations regarding discharge or reassignment. The later ledger contains only names and dates. Also included in this series are records of student nurses and attendants who graduated from the Eastern State Hospital program, including names, dates of graduation, and ceremony programs. For information on early hospital job descriptions, please see Series XVII. Rules, Regulations and Procedures.
  - Employees, Register of, 1907-1930. (Volume 154)
  - Employees, Register of, 1950-1972. (Box 55)
  - Student nurse and attendant graduation records, 1950-1972. (Box 55)
  - Student nurse and attendant graduation records, 1967-1988. (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Series XIV. Photographs, 1931-2007; undated., Extent: 5.425 cu. ft. (Box 56-69.)
  Restricted: Photographs that identify patients or depict medical treatments are restricted for 125 years.
  Contains both black and white and color photographs that document activities, buildings, events, employees, and patients at Eastern State hospital. The photographs depict various activities such as holiday parties, picnics, and special events such as the circus and horse shows. The photos also show the buildings and grounds at both the downtown and Dunbar locations. The employee photographs are mostly head shots, but some also document the receipt of service awards, as well as groups of food service employees, attendants, Grey Ladies (volunteers), and physicians. The Safety Department photos show the demolition of structures, disaster drills, and other safety-related activities.
  Arranged alphabetically by category and then alphabetically by title or description within.
  - Activities
    - Badminton, 1957. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Christmas, 1957-1973. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Christmas, 1977-1982. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Christmas, undated. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Christmas Gift Shop, 1966-1977. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Drawings of ward life, undated. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Easter, 1969; 1975. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Halloween, 1947; 1953. (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Halloween, 1971-1981; undated. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1967. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1972. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1977. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1983. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (circa 1950-1965). (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (circa 1950-1965). (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (circa 1950-1965). (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (circa 1966-1985). (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (no patients), undated (circa 1950-1982). (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (poster boards), undated (circa 1950-1960). (Box 67)
    - Music therapy / Choir, 1948-1953. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Music therapy / Choir, undated (circa 1948-1952). (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Occupational therapy (children), 1966. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Occupational therapy (flower arrangement), 1982; undated (circa 1950-1960). (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Occupational therapy (food preparation), 1947. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Occupational therapy (food preparation), 1948; undated (circa 1948). (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Occupational therapy (food preparation), 1949; 1953. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Occupational therapy (gardening), 1973; 1981; undated (circa 1950). (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Occupational therapy (sewing), 1949; 1951; 1971. (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Occupational therapy (sewing), undated (circa 1948-1955). (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Occupational therapy (weaving), 1948-1949; undated. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Occupational therapy (woodworking and painting), 1949; undated (circa 1949). (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Pet therapy, 1982. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Pool / Swimming, 1972-1979. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Savings Bonds sales, 1969; 1971. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Staged return home of a patient, 1952. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Token economy, 1969-1978. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - United Way campaign, 1969. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds
    - Bathrooms, undated (circa 1950-1955). (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Bell from Thurman Building, 1981. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Brown Building, 1970. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Canteen, 1954; undated. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Cemeteries (printed from a website), 2007. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Dedications, 1961-1975. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Downtown site, 1947-1973. (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Downtown site, undated (circa 1940-1970). (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Downtown site, undated (circa 1940-1970). (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Downtown site, undated (circa 1906-1940). (Box 02)
    - Downtown site, Demolition of, 1952-1969; undated. (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Downtown site, Early postcard images of (copies of drawings), undated. (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Downtown site, Main building (cabinet card), undated (circa 1860-1880). (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Downtown site, Miscellaneous (copies and prints), undated. (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Downtown site in the snow, 1958. (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Dunbar, 1950-1963. (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Dunbar, 1965-1982. (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Dunbar, undated (circa 1940-1980). (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Dunbar, Aerial, 1940s-1992. (Box 02)
    - Dunbar, Miscellaneous (copies and prints), 1969; undated. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Dunbar under construction, undated (circa 1940s). (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Employee Building, 1951; undated. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Exterior Dunbar and Downtown sites, 1931-1952; undated. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Exterior Dunbar and Downtown sites, 1931-1952; undated. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Exterior Dunbar and Downtown sites, 1931-1952; undated. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Exterior Dunbar and Downtown sites, 1931-1952; undated. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Exterior Dunbar and Downtown sites, 1931-1952; undated. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Farm (buildings and animals), 1948. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Farm (buildings and animals), 1952; 1968; undated. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Historical marker, undated. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - "Homelike atmosphere" article, 1976. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Hurricane Hazel damage, 1954. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Laundry renovation, 1983. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Library buildings (photocopies), undated. (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Public Hospital, Drawings and elevations of (copies and prints), undated. (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Receiving Building (Dunbar), 1961. (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Sequeyra Building, 1968. (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Tyler and Brown Buildings, Demolition of, 1954; undated. (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Wards, etc., 1952-1973. (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Wards, etc., undated (circa 1940-1970). (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Employees
    - Attendant / Psychiatric Aide / PPN graduations, 1958-1978; undated. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Attendant training classes (album), 1961-1968. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Awards, 1979-1983. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Chaplain and interns and staff, 1953-1981; undated. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - David Pribble, 1980; undated. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Ashbury, 1960-1963; undated. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Dr. Granville Jones, 1952; undated. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Dr. John M. Galt (bust and portrait), undated. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Dr. Schmidt, 1972-1979. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Employee orientation classes, 1954; undated. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Food Service, 1959-1981. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Food Service, undated (circa 1959-1975). (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Grey Ladies' activities, 1948-1949; undated. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Grey Ladies' activities (with patients), 1948. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Grey Ladies' activities (with patients), 1953-1959; undated. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Grey Ladies' graduation, 1949. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Grounds crew, 1969. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Laboratory Services, undated (circa 1950-1960). (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Laundry workers, 1953. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Maintenance workers, 1953. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Medical Services, 1952. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1956. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1958. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973. (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974. (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975. (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976. (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976. (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977. (Box 61, Folder 21)